Stop what you're doing. You need to pay
attention to this chart because the same
pattern happens every single cycle, just
like clockwork, and it always shocks the
high majority. What I'm going to explain
to you is what is going to happen the
next few months in Bitcoin because it's
going to get wild. I need you to be
ready for it because if you look at
these exact patterns, they match
identically. Take a look at 2015 when we
had this green line cross the yellow
line, we created this gruesome pocket,
and it was an absolute bloodbath. Fast
forward 4 years, 2019, same thing
happened. We had this green line finally
cross through the yellow, we created
this pocket, it was an absolute
bloodbath. Fast forward 4 years, 2022,
we had this cross, we created this
pocket, and we had our absolute
bloodbath. And here we are. We just
recently had our cross, we're starting
to create our pocket, and I'm going to
explain what is about to happen next,
how it's going to shock the world, what
I believe is going to happen, and then
I'm going to tell you what you should do
based on all of the facts and evidence
that I am about to give. Let's get into
it. By the way, we are getting tons of
comments about when bottom and altcoins.
Did you know I give my top altcoin picks
and my big secret investment both
covered in the big Bitcoin Bottom
Blueprint. Just my big secret investment
alone is already worth multiple times
the cost of the Bitcoin Bottom
Blueprint. But on top of that, you get
my top altcoin picks, and on top of
that, you get one guaranteed buy inside
of the golden zone or your money back.
Public launch coming soon. Watch your
email.
Here we are, Bitcoin US Dollar Index,
and today we are on the weekly chart. On
our chart, we have a green line and we
have a yellow line. Two moving averages.
One of them is the 21 MA. That is the
one in green. And we have the 50 MA,
which is the one in yellow. And what we
are looking at is when the green crosses
through the yellow. It's at a very
particular point in the market cycle and
the same patterns
happen after that. They're also the same
patterns before. Take a look. 2015, when
we had this cross, it was after the
market cycle top and price fell all the
way down into that support zone. 2019
was no different. When we had that
cross, it was after the market cycle top
and price had already fallen into that
support zone. 2022 was no different.
When we had that cross, it was after the
market cycle top and price had already
fallen to that support zone. Was it
different this time? No. When we had
that cross, it was after the market
cycle top and we had already fallen into
our support zone. So, what happens next
is like clockwork, but it shocks the
high majority and today I don't want
that to happen to you. So, I'm going to
give you the facts. We're going to cover
the evidence in this chart right here
and then I'm going to tell you what I
think is going to happen and then I'm
going to tell you what you should do
with the information. Now, what I want
you to do is take a mental screenshot of
what we got right now because we also
used this chart 2 months ago when we
were up above 80,000 and we stayed
level-headed thanks to this chart. We've
got to give credit where credit is due
because this chart told us, "Hey,
actually in every single market cycle
bottom, we go above this green line. In
fact, hey, sometimes we actually get all
the way up to the yellow line. So,
that's exactly what we covered in a
video a couple months ago where we said,
"Hey, we're above this green line.
There's no worry. We do that every
single cycle. The bear market will
continue. Our pocket will continue." And
here we are 2 months later. And what
we've noticed is we're at an absolute
breaking point and this thing could get
wild. Let me show you. So, what I want
you to do is understand how many days in
we are. And we'll start to really
understand where we are at present day.
We're at 170 days after the cross.
Remember that. Put that number, put it
in your memory bank. It's going to be
incredibly important. Now, we're going
to take a look at the facts for 2015 in
this circle we have and 2019 in that
circle and 2022. And we're going to
start to piece together new information.
And we're going to start to piece
together these new facts and we're going
to have a very good idea about the
patterns that play out. And then we're
going to look at about 168 days in, 180
days in of when this is going to happen
and what happens next. Recently, many of
you have been randomly unsubscribed from
my channel. And missing just one video
in a market like this can cost you big
time. So, stop what you're doing, look
down, and make sure you are subscribed.
So, we start our journey in 2015. Now,
in 2015, you can see the 21 moving
average crossing the 50 moving average
on the weekly chart at precisely August
2014. What we notice is that after that
cross had happened, we We had multiple
rallies in the market. Multiple.
Multiple up to the green, multiple a
little bit over the green, and we had
one even get up to the yellow. But, it
all ended the same exact way. Towards
that big opening of our gap, that's when
we saw the bottom of the market. But,
more importantly, how many days was it?
Because what we notice in the market is
that when this green line comes and
crosses back up, it marks one of the
best buying opportunities ever in
Bitcoin. And I'm going to cover more on
that later, but you can just look. Every
single time we had the green line cross
here, green line cross here, back up, it
represented amazing times to buy. So,
how long is that wait period? From the
time that we had our cross and we create
a bloodbath to the time that we had a
cross back up and we have the best
buying opportunity ever. Well, let's do
a little measured move. We're going to
measure from when we cross down to when
we crossed back up, and we notice it's
roughly 400 days. In other words, when
we have that cross down, the bloodbath
happens, but about 400 days later,
the bloodbath is over. And this cross
back up marks the end of our worry, the
end of our bloodbath, and the beginning
of the next bull.
So, if you want to know when the next
real pump is going to happen, look no
further than this chart. In fact, I hope
you pause this video right now and pull
up this chart and plug these settings in
and so you can look at it live as we're
discussing it together because that will
help you stay level-headed more than
anything. You should throw social media
away and focus on facts. The system is
what creates success, and the systems
that I've built here keep us
level-headed. So, we notice, okay,
there's a 400-day
window. In other words, during that 400
days, we plummet in price, we see a
bloodbath, but we have our bottom, and
then we cross to start the new bull. How
about the next cycle? 2019, we had our
50 MA right here, the yellow line, and
we have that 21 MA cross right through
back in July 2018. And what you notice,
the same kind of things. We rallied. We
rallied above the green, we rallied all
the way to the yellow, but it wasn't a
concern because the bear market
continued. And this green line sort of
took our head and shoved it down. And
the green line just kept pushing our
head down until we finally met our
market cycle bottom. You have this big
gap here, and then we moved above here
back in June. 2019, we had the green
line cross back up marking the beginning
of the bull. But how long was that
period? Because we noticed 2015 was
about 400 days. How about this period?
This period was also roughly
400-ish days from the point when we had
that cross down to the point of that
cross up, roughly a 400-ish day period
of when we go from absolute turmoil to
the best moment that we've all been
waiting for for years, which is the
start of the next bull run. In 2022, it
was more of the same. You can see this
green line right here and crossing
through back in March 2022. It likes to
cross roughly every 4 years, and when it
does, you can see what happened, right?
We had a short-term rally. We rallied
above the green, we rallied even up to
that yellow, but again, that green just
kept pushing our head down, and it was
not a very fair battle. But once again,
roughly 400-ish days of this period
between gruesome and the start of the
bull. Keep in mind the start of the bull
happened here roughly $25,000
in our recent cycle. And we went from
about $25,000
up to $126,000
before we saw the same pattern happen.
We crossed back down through this yellow
after the market had already topped.
Every single time in every single market
when we have this green line crossed
through, it's after the market had
already topped. Then we have about a 400
day period before our next bull run. So,
I've got a good news. We are almost
halfway through the chaos between when
the chaos really gets bad and when the
next bull run starts. That's the good
news I want to lay on you right now. So,
no matter what's happening in your mind,
what you're thinking about the market,
what's happening to your portfolio,
there is no time like the beginning of
the bull. That's the best time of the
best time of the best time. And we are
almost there. We are halfway almost
through all of this chaos before the
next bull run starts. That's the good
news. Now, let's get to the bad news,
all right? And you better be sitting
down because you can see these patterns
are repeating patterns. They happen
every single market and it's not pretty.
So, I mentioned that 400 day period. We
know that roughly it's a rough 400 day
period. Sometimes it's 350, but we're
100 and 80-ish days, 100 and something
like that. We're a little bit less than
200 days. So, as you measure it, we're a
little bit less than 200 days and now
things are heating up because we
understand when does that period take us
to? I want to cover a few things next. I
want to cover what I think is going to
happen, when I think the next bull is
going to start, and what you should do
with this information. So, let's cover
those three things. They're incredibly
important. What I think is going to
happen, when I think the next bull is
going to start, and what should you do
with that information? Let's unravel
both. We'll start with the first one.
What do I think is going to happen next?
I think it's more of the same. There's a
hotly debated topic that the bottom is
already in. You know, I support
everybody with their different charts,
etc., etc. But, I have been in a certain
camp for months and months and months
and months and months. And, I will only
change my opinion if the facts in the
charts change. And, the only fact that
can change my opinion is a swing high
higher than 97. Because, functionally in
the chart, that would change everybody's
thesis. It's the biggest fact that could
come in. And, anything less than that,
any rally that's less than 97 is 1,000%
irrelevant, and it will roll over and do
more of the same, which is what every
bear market does ever known to man for
Bitcoin. I showed you all the facts.
2015, exact patterns. 2019, exact
patterns. 2022, exact patterns. And,
we're living in it right now. So far,
it's been the exact same patterns.
There's been absolutely nothing
different about what's happened in the
past handful of months. It's been
exactly what is supposed to happen. So,
what do I expect to happen the next
handful of months for the rest of this
year? We're going to see the bottom of
the market. It's going to get ugly. It's
going to get gruesome. We're going to
have a big pocket. But, then I'll show
you when the next bull is going to
start. Because, that is when things get
very interesting. So, I let you know
what I think is going to happen. It's
going to be more of the same. It's going
to heat up a little bit. But, how about,
more importantly, when will the next
bull potentially start? If you take this
and extrapolate it out, we're looking
at, you know, sometimes this thing
happens, you know, roughly 300, 330, 350
days, you know, sometimes 400 days. In
other words, we're looking at a very
specific
range of time for the next bull run to
start. And it will happen by surprise.
It will catch everyone off guard. People
will not be ready, but it's scheduled to
start towards the end of 2026
or in Q1 in 2027. During that range is
when the next bull run is going to
start. Now, to the most important thing
in today's episode. What should you do
with this information? Number one, you
should start saving up your money and
getting smart about investing. What I
need you to do is trade way, way, way,
way, way less and I want you to really
double down on buying in a window, in
the golden zone window near the bottom
of the market. And then I need you to
think about a couple years later selling
near the top of that market, the top
window. In other words, you only make
decisions every couple years and you
don't make a lot of decisions, you make
a few. And each one carries much more
weight. In other words, instead of
swinging at every pitch, which is what
you've been doing for years, you're
going to take only one swing every
couple years and it counts so much. So,
when that ball comes that you love to
hit, it's right in your sweet spot and
you know you're going to slam it, that's
what you go for. Instead of swinging,
swinging, hoping, swinging, hoping,
swinging, swinging, hoping with no
strategy, it's not strategic. It's not
in that bottom window. It's not in that
top window. You're in and out. You're
emotional. It's an emotional roller
coaster on social media. One day you
think this, one day you think that. This
person thinks that, so you go with that.
All of that is behind you and now you're
more strategic. And now you're more
buttoned up and you will see the
results. So, what do I want you to do
with this information? I want you to get
ready for the next bull run. That's
That's That's that moment of time. And
obviously, I put together my blueprint
to the bottom. And if you really want
success and you want to skip 10 years of
headaches, you get the bottom blueprint
and you'll have it for life. And it will
unlock a brand new future. I'll leave
you on that note. By the way, we are
getting tons of comments about when
bottom and altcoins. Did you know I give
my top altcoin picks and my big secret
investment both covered in the Bitcoin
Bottom Blueprint. Just my big secret
investment alone is already worth
multiple times the cost of the Bitcoin
Bottom Blueprint. But on top of that,
you get my top altcoin picks. And on top
of that, you get one guaranteed buy
inside of the golden zone or your money
back. Public launch coming soon. Watch
your email.